<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>176941</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/176941-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Sherlock is a British television crime drama that presents a contemporary adaptation of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's Sherlock Holmes detective stories. Created by Steven Moffat and Mark Gatiss, it stars Benedict Cumberbatch as Sherlock Holmes and Martin Freeman as Doctor John Watson.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-07-25</FirstAired>
<Network>BBC One</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1475582</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>SH01304269</zap2it_id>
<id>176941</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>281067</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Holmes: Incident at Victoria Falls</SeriesName>
<Overview>King Edward ask Sherlock Holmes to perform one more task before his retirement: to safeguard the Star of Africa on a trip to Cape Town. Soon the fabled jewel is stolen and several people end up being murdered.</Overview>
<IMDB_ID>tt0102115</IMDB_ID>
<id>281067</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>73082</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Hound</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Meitantei Holmes</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/73082-g3.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Loosely based on the "Sherlock Holmes" series by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, Sherlock Hound turns all the classic characters into dogs. The canine Sherlock Holmes, his assistant Watson, and housemaid Mrs. Hudson work together to solve mysteries. The culprit is usually Professor Moriarty and his gang, who use all kinds of wacky contraptions to steal what they want.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1984-11-06</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0088109</IMDB_ID>
<id>73082</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>212991</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Holmes (1991)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/212991-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Christopher Lee and Patrick McNee star as the world's favorite detectives Holmes and Watson. They end up getting into many adventures together during their investigations.</Overview>
<id>212991</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>266997</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Yack - Zoo Detective</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/266997-g2.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>2011-05-04</FirstAired>
<Network>TF1</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2111893</IMDB_ID>
<id>266997</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>71976</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Holmes (1965)</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's Sherlock Holmes</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/71976-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Sherlock Holmes (alternately Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's Sherlock Holmes) was a series of Sherlock Holmes adaptations produced by British television company BBC between 1965 and 1968. In 1964, an adaptation of "The Adventure of the Speckled Band" was commissioned as a pilot for a twelve part series of Sherlock Holmes stories. Douglas Wilmer was cast as Holmes and Nigel Stock as Watson. Peter Cushing was approached to take over the role of Sherlock Holmes for the 1968 series. Only 6 Episodes survived.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1968-09-01</FirstAired>
<Network>BBC One</Network>
<id>71976</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>77728</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sherlock Holmes (1984)</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes|The Return of Sherlock Holmes|The Casebook of Sherlock Holmes|The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes|The Sign of Four|The Hound of the Baskervilles</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/77728-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>This series (made by Granada between 1984 and 1994) featuring the late Jeremy Brett as the eponymous detective includes The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes, The Return of Sherlock Holmes, The Casebook of Sherlock Holmes, The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes, The Sign of Four, and The Hound of the Baskervilles. Granada Television had set themselves the task of filming every one of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's Sherlock Holmes stories. A number of the mysteries were still waiting to be filmed at Jeremy Brett's death in 1995, but Granada decided not to continue without him.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1984-04-24</FirstAired>
<Network>ITV1</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0086661</IMDB_ID>
<id>77728</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>261925</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Case-Book Of Sherlock Holmes</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/261925-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Sherlock Holmes and his intrepid companion, Dr. Watson solve mysteries and disappearances.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1991-02-21</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0098765</IMDB_ID>
<id>261925</id>
</Series>
</Data>