<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>80572</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Yo</SeriesName>
<id>80572</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>285878</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Jyuuisan jiken desu yo</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>2014-07-03</FirstAired>
<Network>YTV</Network>
<id>285878</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>262112</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Say "I Love You"</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Say I Love You|Suki-tte Ii na yo.|Sukitte Ii na yo.</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/262112-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The story of first love centers around Mei Tachibana, a girl who has never made friends or had a boyfriend in 16 years. One day, she accidentally injures Yamato Kurosawa, the school's most popular boy. For some reason, Yamato becomes interested in Mei and starts a one-sided friendship with her. He even protects her from a stalker — by kissing her.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-10-07</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2309312</IMDB_ID>
<id>262112</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>264531</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Problem Children Are Coming from Another World, Aren't They?</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Mondai-Ji-tachi ga Isekai kara Kuru Sou Desu yo?|Don't Problem Children Come From an Alternate World?|Mondaiji tachi ga Isekai kara Kuru soudesuyo?</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/264531-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The story follows Sakamaki Izayoi, a boy bored with the entire world. One day, an envelope arrives for him. The moment Izayoi opens the envelope, he is transported to an alternate world. There, he discovers that two other problem children were transported by envelopes as well — a taciturn girl named Kasukabe You with a cat, and a beautiful yet haughty girl named Kudou Asuka. A girl named Kuro Usagi (Black Rabbit) summoned the three to the community No Name to overthrow the devil.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2013-01-12</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2575690</IMDB_ID>
<id>264531</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>173301</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Cat Planet Cuties</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Asobi ni Iku Yo! |Asobi ni Ikuyo: Bombshells from the Sky</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/173301-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The story revolves around Kakazu Kio, an ordinary high school freshman living in Okinawa. A girl with cat ears appears before him during a memorial service for one of his family ancestors. The girl calls herself Eris and claims she is an alien. Before long, fanatical alien worshippers and a mysterious government agency are in hot pursuit of Eris, but Kio's childhood friend Manami — who wants to follow in her father's footsteps in the CIA — captures Eris. Kio finds himself having to protect Eris from everyone.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2010-07-10</FirstAired>
<Network>MBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1694025</IMDB_ID>
<id>173301</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>247911</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>You're Being Summoned, Azazel-san</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Yondemasu yo, Azazel-san|Yondemasuyo, Azazel-san</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/247911-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Akutabe, a detective, summons devils to solve the troubles of his clients. One day, a low class devil Azazel Atsushi is summoned by Akutabe and is used harshly by him and his assistant Rinko Sakuma.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-04-08</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo MX</Network>
<id>247911</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>253157</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Sexy Commando Gaiden: Sugoi yo!! Masaru-san</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Sekushi Commando Gaiden: Sugoiyo! Masaru-san</AliasNames>
<Overview>Okometsubu Fujiyama has recently transferred over to a new school, Wakame High School. His goal is to make 100 friends--until he meets the extremely wierd Masaru Hananakajima. Masaru is a martial artist whose specialty is the "Sexy Commando" form of martial art. Masaru forms a club based on this art, including Fujiyama, who he nicknames Fuumin, in the club. The club becomes full of strange, yet wacky people. Aliens, moustaches, and cute fuzzy animals are encountered as the club moves along and gets steadily more popular.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-01-01</FirstAired>
<Network>Tokyo Broadcasting System</Network>
<id>253157</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>262092</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>OniAi</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Onii-chan Dakedo Ai Sae Areba Kankeinai yo ne!</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/262092-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>After 6-years' separation, Himenokouji Akito reunites with his twin sister Akiko and they live together once more. However, in the interim, Akiko had developed a serious case of bro-con, romantic feelings for Akito.

It doesn't stop there as Nikaidou Arashi, the student council president of his new school, vice-president Nasuhara Anastasia, and Sawatari Ginbei Haruomi, who followed Akito all the way from Kyoto, all move in with him one after the other.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-10-05</FirstAired>
<Network>AT-X</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2390038</IMDB_ID>
<id>262092</id>
</Series>
</Data>