<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>81184</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Rosario + Vampire</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Rosario to Vampire</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/81184-g5.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Due to poor grades, Tsukune Aono, an average high school student, has been unable to get accepted into any private academy of his choice. By exceptional accident, the only school to accept him turns out to be anything but ordinary; the school is attended by youkai disguised as humans. Fearing for his life, he attempts to escape only to meet Moka Akashiya, a beautiful girl who just happens to be a vampire. Despite this, Tsukune decides to stay at the academy, hiding his human nature from students and teachers. Tsukune also discovers that when the rosary around Moka's neck is removed, her true nature emerges.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2008-01-03</FirstAired>
<Network>CTC</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1821149</IMDB_ID>
<id>81184</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>252394</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Vampire Prosecutor</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Vampire Geumsa|Vampire Prosecutor 2</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/252394-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Min Tae Yeon (Yun Jung Hoon) isn't your typical vampire or your typical prosecutor. Rather than drinking blood from innocent strangers, he opts for blood sold on the black market in the posh bars of Seoul. He also has the uncanny ability to tell where the victim of his cases died, and how they died based on their blood's smell and taste. The only person who knows of his secret ability is Detective Hwang Soon Bum (Lee Won Jong). They end up working together in a new joint department between police and prosecutors solving murder cases. They are joined by rookie prosecutor Yoo Jung In (Lee Young Ah), and intern Cho Dong Man.

Together, they solve murder cases, and Tae Yeon must use his "powers" to find leads on seemingly unsolvable cases. The one mystery he can't solve is: who was the vampire/serial killer that changed him seven years ago? </Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-10-02</FirstAired>
<Network>OCN</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt2368922</IMDB_ID>
<id>252394</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>149421</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Master of Mosquiton '99</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Master Mosquiton</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/149421-g.jpg</banner>
<FirstAired>1997-09-30</FirstAired>
<Network>TV Tokyo</Network>
<id>149421</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>85274</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Vampire Host</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Bloodhound: The Vampire Host|Vampire Gigolo</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/85274-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>“Rion, help me! A real vampire…”

That was the last cell message Rion heard from her friend Shiho before she disappeared. Determined to find out what became of her, Rion searches Shiho’s room and uncovers a business card for a local host club.

Kranken Haus, an ornate entertainment club for women, is filled with handsome men costumed as vampires who serve as bartenders and escorts for females desiring company and attention.

She confronts Suou, a gorgeous man working at the club as a host, whose name is on the card. He denies any involvement with her disappearance and tries to brush her off. Rion concocts an incident and starts working there too so she can keep an eye on him and the club owner. But things get complicated when it’s revealed that Suou isn’t just acting – he really is a 200-year-old vampire!

That’s only the beginning in this horror-comedy live-action series that is based on a best-selling Japanese manga.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2004-04-04</FirstAired>
<Network>TV Tokyo</Network>
<id>85274</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>248972</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>My Babysitter's a Vampire</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/248972-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The series follows the adventures of a geeky freshman boy named Ethan Morgan (Matthew Knight), a Seer who has visions when he touches anything paranormal, his best friend Benny (Atticus Mitchell), a spellmaster, and his vampire babysitter Sarah (Vanessa Morgan) as they chase down supernatural forces. They are often aided by Rory (Cameron Kennedy), their dorky friend who was turned into a vampire in the pilot film, and Erica (Kate Todd), Sarah's best friend, who also became a vampire in the pilot film.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-02-28</FirstAired>
<Network>Disney Channel</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1727434</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01417690</zap2it_id>
<id>248972</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>224881</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>My Date With a Vampire</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>My Date with a Vampire II|My Date with a Vampire III</AliasNames>
<Overview>Fong (Eric Wan) is a Chinese resistance fighter from the time of the Second Sino-Japanese War. In 1938, he was fighting with a Japanese lieutenant when they were interrupted by the appearance of the Vampire King. The two men and a boy named Fok Sung living the nearby village were bitten and they become vampires. These vampires are creatures that exist beyond the Three Dimensions (Heaven, Earth and Humanity) and Six realms, where all other beings, including animals, humans, deities and spirits, exist.
In present-day 1998, Fong lives in Hong Kong under a new name. His physical appearance has not changed since 60 years ago. Fong works as a policeman and Fok Sung lives together with him as his "son", who currently attends primary school. Ma Siu-Ling (Joey Meng) is a ghostbuster from the Ma family, which has co-operated with the Taoist Mao family for generations in ridding the world of evil supernatural beings. Ma falls in love with Fong and they begin an epic love story which withstands the test of time.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1998-11-30</FirstAired>
<id>224881</id>
</Series>
</Data>