<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
<Series>
<seriesid>291437</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Endless Game</SeriesName>
<id>291437</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>234461</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Lying Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/234461-g5.jpg</banner>
<Overview>The Lying Game follows Emma, a kind-hearted foster kid who learns she has an identical twin sister, Sutton. Sutton, unlike Emma, was adopted by wealthy parents and is seemingly living an ideal life. After their initial meeting, Sutton talks Emma into stepping into her life for a few days while she pursues a lead on the mysterious identity of their birth mother. After Sutton inexplicably fails to return to the girls' designated meeting place, Emma must decide whether to come clean about her identity and risk her own safety in the hope of uncovering her twin sister's whereabouts, along with the truth about why they were separated in the first place.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2011-08-15</FirstAired>
<Network>ABC Family</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1798274</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP01400124</zap2it_id>
<id>234461</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>90681</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Dirt Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/90681-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>UK oil executive Brian Jardine (Gerald Lepkowski) and Australian geologist Megan Kerr (Freya Stafford) have been given six months to turn the company’s fortunes around. Up for the challenge is a strongly committed specialist team made up of engineer Max Mees (Shane Connor), ex-unionist Shane Bevic (Joel Edgerton) and former environmentalist Caz Cohen (Katie Wall), With boardroom backstabbing, growing safety and environmental issues, financial pressures and employee unrest, the odds are stacked against them. </Overview>
<FirstAired>2009-04-19</FirstAired>
<Network>ABC (AU)</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1325886</IMDB_ID>
<id>90681</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>292233</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Game Changers</SeriesName>
<Overview>Celebrating athletes and fans who give back to their communities making life better for so many,  GAME CHANGERS, hosted by “The Insider’s” Kevin Frazier, highlights professional athletes who use their public image to make positive changes in the lives of fans in need. Young reporters seek  their stories from the field, and bring back journalistic gold to the GAME CHANGERS studios to culminate in heartfelt reflection and insight from the host.  Whether on or off the field, GAME CHANGERS takes an inspirational look at how sports positively impact individuals and the communities they serve.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2013-09-28</FirstAired>
<Network>CBS</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3214726</IMDB_ID>
<id>292233</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>81443</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Good Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/81443-g3.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Good Game is a show by gamers for gamers. Each week it will be jam-packed with the latest gaming news and events, top gaming tips, reviews and interviews with game developers and the people behind the scenes. 

Hosted by Bajo and Hex, Good Game is filmed in the Den of Gaming; a gamers' paradise fitted out with just about every gaming device ever invented and complemented by a huge plasma screen.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-09-19</FirstAired>
<Network>ABC2</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0978036</IMDB_ID>
<id>81443</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>259930</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>The Racing Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/259930-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Crime-mystery drama series featuring an ex-jockey turned private detective. Series based on stories by author Dick Francis. GB. Yorkshire Television.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1979-11-21</FirstAired>
<Network>ITV</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt007865</IMDB_ID>
<id>259930</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>84089</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Harry's Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/84089-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>A British Cabinet Minister is gunned down outside his home in London by a member of the Provisional IRA. Security protocols are activated, but the assassin evades them and successfully escapes to Belfast. In the aftermath of the incident, rash decisions are made by politicians seeking revenge, and the Ministry of Defence responds by sending Captain Harry Brown (Ray Lonnen) - a special forces soldier who has done deep cover work in hostile territory - into the Falls Road area of Belfast, notorious for civil unrest and Republican activity. Harry's mission is to infiltrate the local nationalist population, uncover the identity of the assassin, and kill him in his own neighborhood - proving to the IRA that they are not safe, even in their "own back yard". But as his relentless search becomes more desperate, an innocent girl's life is claimed. The IRA soon realizes they have an informant in their area and brings in the same assassin, Billy Downes (Derek Thompson), to hunt down Harry. The situation develops into a deadly game of cat and mouse in which more innocent lives will be affected and neither side can win.</Overview>
<FirstAired>1982-12-13</FirstAired>
<IMDB_ID>tt0084053</IMDB_ID>
<id>84089</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>284039</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Reset</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Crying Game|Ten Days Ago</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/284039-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Prosecutor Cha Woo Jin lost his first love, Kim Seung Hee 15 years ago. He then meets a high school girl, Jo Eun Bi, who looks like his first love. Their meeting unleashed secrets and chain of events between Cha Woo Jin, Seung Hee, Jo Eun Bi, and the criminal.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2014-08-10</FirstAired>
<Network>OCN</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt3873672</IMDB_ID>
<id>284039</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>84099</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>America's Game</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>NFL Videos: America's Game</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/84099-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>America's Game: The Super Bowl Champions is an annual documentary series created by NFL Films (broadcast on the NFL Network and CBS). Its 42 installments profile the first 42 winning teams of the National Football League's annual Super Bowl championship game in, each episode chronicals an individual team.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2006-11-17</FirstAired>
<Network>NFL Network</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt1213209</IMDB_ID>
<zap2it_id>EP00813210</zap2it_id>
<id>84099</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>92231</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Full Tilt's Million Dollar Cash Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/92231-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>In collaboration with team Full Tilt, the Emblaze Production team launched and produced Europe’s first ever televised game of high-stakes poker. The minimum amount of cash players could sit down with was a staggering $100,000.

Million Dollar Cash Game features the biggest names from the world of Poker including Phil Ivey, Gus Hansen, Eric Seidel, Howard Lederer, Chris Ferguson, Jennifer Harmon, Allen Cunningham and Mike Matusow.

</Overview>
<id>92231</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>257870</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Game On! (2012)</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/257870-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Veronica Belmont &amp; Brian Brushwood can’t live without video games. They’d literally die. TWiT’s first video game show, Game On, fixes this. They are sustained by playing games and then gleefully bringing you news, reviews and commentary about console and PC games that you can get nowhere else. Please watch Game On, it’s a matter of life and death.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2012-01-16</FirstAired>
<id>257870</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>120351</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>Akahori's Heretical Hour Love Game</SeriesName>
<banner>graphical/120351-g.jpg</banner>
<Overview>Rabuge flips back-and-forth following the tribulations of two groups of women: Ayumi and Kaoruko, AKA "Love Pheromone," a pair of heroines who fight for justice but always cause more chaos than good, and the Hokke Sisters, five girls who make up the Gedou Otome-Tai, bent on spreading evil throughout the world, but end up helping others instead. Both Love Pheromone and Gedou Otome-Tai struggle through poverty while attempting to reach their goals, be they becoming the world's greatest evil, or to become a popular comedy group and have legions of fans.</Overview>
<FirstAired>2005-07-05</FirstAired>
<id>120351</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>75266</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>A Mug's Game</SeriesName>
<FirstAired>1996-01-01</FirstAired>
<id>75266</id>
</Series>
<Series>
<seriesid>84501</seriesid>
<language>en</language>
<SeriesName>GameCenter CX</SeriesName>
<AliasNames>Retro Game Master</AliasNames>
<banner>graphical/84501-g2.jpg</banner>
<Overview>GameCenter CX (domestically imported as Retro Game Master) is a Japanese television series where Shinya Arino, a member of comedy duo Yoiko, plays Japan's most popular video games (a majority of which are Famicom games) and records his progress as he works through a time limit, usually lasting up to one day. He is supported by his Assistant Directors (herein referred to as ADs) and Staff, both via moral support and actual gameplay.

He also gets the chance to interview game designers and to play arcade games occasionally.
</Overview>
<FirstAired>2003-11-04</FirstAired>
<Network>Fuji TV</Network>
<IMDB_ID>tt0969664</IMDB_ID>
<id>84501</id>
</Series>
</Data>